[{"answer": "Hey listen, let me give you my card. It's got my home number on it. I want to buy the first pair when the next shipment comes in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "All right my friend talking to ya", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Aahhrgh...it wouldn't take. Ten minutes from now, I'll be sweating all over again, I can feel it. I'm a human heat pump", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Cold showers? They're for psychotics. my friend Well I take 'em........They give me a Whooooosh", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " my friend , I really don't...............pay much attention to me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No... I find them repugnant and unappealing. my friend bursts i", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Hmm! Oh! Yeah. I'll tell you who is an attractive ma", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " You know those shoes that my friend had? I cut a deal with him. We're gonna import a case of them together", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "There's a lot of money in this.. He's got a proven sales metho", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hey! What's this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "......that place........ my friend at the health club trying to attract the handsome blond guy's attention", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You know...my friend is pretty sweet on you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh yeah!. my friend's been watching you....you're just my friend's type", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend's new in town. my friend hem ..doesn't really know anyone", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend would like to get to know you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well.. Aye can't hold the water. my friend comes in dribbling", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Hey my frien", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well apparently I do something 'cause I'm sitting at the head table with Mr. my friend sits on the couch and puts his feet up on the coffee table", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Ehmm ..These are my vertical leap training shoes", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You know! Like a tennis shirt", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Sometimes I tuck'em sometimes I don'", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Sometimes I tuck'em sometimes I don'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I think I was tucked.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Ughhh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What are you gettin'", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey, by the way, did you ever call that guy from the health club.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How so", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What's that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Jimmy.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No no you said my friend likes spicy chicken", "qsentId": 32}]